{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "10 + 5 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"]
        },
        {
            "question": "15 + 8 =",
            "answer": "23",
            "options": ["22", "23", "24", "25"]
        },
        {
            "question": "20 + 4 =",
            "answer": "24",
            "options": ["22", "23", "24", "25"]
        },
        {
            "question": "22 + 6 =",
            "answer": "28",
            "options": ["28", "29", "30", "31"]
        },
        {
            "question": "26 + 4 =",
            "answer": "30",
            "options": ["29", "30", "31", "32"]
        },
        {
            "question": "13 + 7 =",
            "answer": "20",
            "options": ["19", "20", "21", "22"]
        },
        {
            "question": "30 + 5 =",
            "answer": "35",
            "options": ["34", "35", "36", "37"]
        },
        {
            "question": "14 + 11 =",
            "answer": "25",
            "options": ["24", "25", "26", "27"]
        },
        {
            "question": "28 + 2 =",
            "answer": "30",
            "options": ["30", "29", "28", "27"]
        },
        {
            "question": "7 + 3 =",
            "answer": "10",
            "options": ["10", "11", "12", "13"]
        },
        {
            "question": "6 + 9 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["15", "16", "17", "18"]
        },
        {
            "question": "17 + 8 =",
            "answer": "25",
            "options": ["23", "24", "25", "26"]
        },
        {
            "question": "15 - 8 =",
            "answer": "7",
            "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"]
        },
        {
            "question": "25 - 6 =",
            "answer": "19",
            "options": ["19", "18", "17", "16"]
        },
        {
            "question": "18 - 9 =",
            "answer": "9",
            "options": ["8", "9", "10", "11"]
        },
        {
            "question": "30 - 14 =",
            "answer": "16",
            "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"]
        },
        {
            "question": "27 - 12 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["13", "14", "15", "16"]
        },
        {
            "question": "22 - 7 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"]
        },
        {
            "question": "31 - 16 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"]
        },
        {
            "question": "20 - 3 =",
            "answer": "17",
            "options": ["17", "18", "19", "20"]
        },
        {
            "question": "12 x 11 =",
            "answer": "132",
            "options": ["132", "122", "112", "142"]
        },
        {
            "question": "17 x 15 =",
            "answer": "255",
            "options": ["255", "265", "275", "285"]
        },
        {
            "question": "23 x 14 =",
            "answer": "322",
            "options": ["312", "322", "332", "342"]
        },
        {
            "question": "36 x 18 =",
            "answer": "648",
            "options": ["648", "658", "668", "678"]
        },
        {
            "question": "42 x 27 =",
            "answer": "1134",
            "options": ["1134", "1144", "1154", "1164"]
        },
        {
            "question": "51 x 19 =",
            "answer": "969",
            "options": ["969", "979", "989", "999"]
        },
        {
            "question": "64 x 13 =",
            "answer": "832",
            "options": ["822", "842", "852", "832"]
        },
        {
            "question": "88 x 22 =",
            "answer": "1936",
            "options": ["1926", "1946", "1956", "1936"]
        },
        {
            "question": "79 x 15 =",
            "answer": "1185",
            "options": ["1175", "1185", "1195", "1205"]
        },
        {
            "question": "132 ÷ 12 =",
            "answer": "11",
            "options": ["10", "11", "12", "13"]
        },
        {
            "question": "315 ÷ 21 =",
            "answer": "15",
            "options": ["15", "14", "16", "17"]
        },
        {
            "question": "864 ÷ 24 =",
            "answer": "36",
            "options": ["34", "35", "36", "37"]
        },
        {
            "question": "420 ÷ 20 =",
            "answer": "21",
            "options": ["20", "21", "22", "23"]
        },
        {
            "question": "357 ÷ 17 =",
            "answer": "21",
            "options": ["20", "22", "23", "21"]
        },
        {
            "question": "625 ÷ 25 =",
            "answer": "25",
            "options": ["23", "24", "25", "26"]
        },
        {
            "question": "12 + (7+8) x 5 =",
            "answer": "87",
            "options": ["85", "86", "87", "88"]
        },
        {
            "question": "4 x (15 – 13) + 16 =",
            "answer": "24",
            "options": ["24", "25", "26", "27"]
        },
        {
            "question": "12 x 3 + (100 ÷10) =",
            "answer": "46",
            "options": ["43", "44", "45", "46"]
        },
        {
            "question": "(9 -2) + (3 x 10) + 7 =",
            "answer": "44",
            "options": ["43", "44", "45", "46"]
        },
        {
            "question": "(93 + 7) x 6 + 10 =",
            "answer": "610",
            "options": ["610", "620", "630", "640"]
        },
        {
            "question": "6 + 7 x 8 =",
            "answer": "62",
            "options": ["104", "62", "22", "108"]
        },
        {
            "question": "8 ÷ 2 (5 + 16) – 6 =",
            "answer": "118",
            "options": ["118", "19", "60", "30"]
        },
        {
            "question": "3 + 6 x (5 + 4) ÷ 3 =",
            "answer": "21",
            "options": ["16", "12", "21", "61"]
        },
        {
            "question": "9 + 3 x (8 + 7) + 9 =",
            "answer": "45",
            "options": ["45", "36", "49", "35"]
        },
        {
            "question": "20 – 4 + 6 x 3 =",
            "answer": "34",
            "options": ["66", "34", "2", "10"]
        },
        {
            "question": "37 + 3 x 2 ÷ 6 =",
            "answer": "38",
            "options": ["13", "7", "46", "38"]
        },
        {
            "question": "24 x 6 - 2 + 5 x 2 =",
            "answer": "152",
            "options": ["152", "294", "142", "249"]
        },
        {
            "question": "82 + 9 x 9 + 20 =",
            "answer": "183",
            "options": ["839", "183", "389", "381"]
        },
        {
            "question": "36 - 6 x 5 =",
            "answer": "6",
            "options": ["150", "100", "6", "9"]
        },
        {
            "question": "4 x (8 x 5) + 17 =",
            "answer": "177",
            "options": ["177", "157", "167", "187"]
        }
    ]
}
